https://www.pfyc.com/privacy-policy.html

Other Stuff
On Sale Now!
Other Stuff
On Sale Now!
Other Stuff
On Sale Now!
Other Stuff
On Sale Now!
Other Stuff
Parts On Sale Now!
Other Stuff
Parts On Sale Now!
Other Stuff
Parts On Sale Now!
MagnaFlow Exhaust Systems
More...
Privacy Policy
At PartsForYourCar.com ("PFYC"), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read the text below for more details about our privacy policy (the "Policy"). This Policy governs this Web site and other Web sites and Web pages operated by PFYC (the "PFYC Site" and collectively, the "PFYC Sites").
Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted in this section (Privacy Statement) of the Web site, as well as other appropriate locations to ensure our customers understand how their information is being collected, used and disclosed. We will always use any information collected in accordance with the privacy policy in place at the time the information was collected.
NOTE TO CHILDREN UNDER 13: YOU ARE NOT ELIGIBLE TO USE THE SERVICES OR PURCHASE PRODUCTS ON THIS SITE. PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE US WITH ANY INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF.
Tell us what you think
PFYC welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please contact us online or by U.S. Mail.
Frequently Asked Questions about Privacy
1Q.	What information do we collect and how is it used?
2Q.	What about "Cookies"?
3Q.	Will PFYC disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
4Q.	How does PFYC protect customer information?
5Q.	How does PFYC allow customers to update or change the information it collects?
6Q.	How does PFYC protect children's privacy?
7Q.	What about links to other web sites and services?
8Q.	How does PFYC.com have my consent to use this information?
1A.	What information do we collect and how is it used?
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. Your credit card information is maintained by our secure credit card processor and is not stored by PFYC.
When you sign-up for our e-mail notification service, we need only an e-mail address, which we use to send the requested information. You may unsubscribe to this list at any time by sending a message to "unsubscribe" as explained in each newsletter.
We monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of our stores.
We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the PFYC sites, new PFYC services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. However, we will only do this if you have opted-in to receive these mailings. If at any time you decide you no longer wish to receive them, you can always opt-out by following the instructions at the bottom of each mailing.
2A.	What about "Cookies"?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information but are used to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Many computers automatically accept cookies, but you can opt to prevent that. Please note, however, that without cookies, you will not be able to shop at the PFYC sites, because our shopping cart software currently uses cookies to temporarily store the items you've selected for purchase.
3A.	Will PFYC disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
PFYC does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. PFYC may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifyable information.
PFYC may release personally identifiable information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of PFYC, our users or others.
In the event that PFYC completes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company or selling a portion of its assets, users' information, in most instances, will be a part of the assets transferred. Such a transfer shall not be considered a violation of or deviation from this Policy.
4A.	How does PFYC protect customer information?
When you place orders, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information that you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, we have implemented security measures to protect customer data we collect against unauthorized access.
5A.	How does PFYC allow customers to update or change the information it collects?
You may update or change information related to your PFYC account by logging in to your account through the My Account section and then changing and saving your updated information.
If at any time you would like us to remove you from our e-mail or postal mailing lists, feel free to contact us.
6A.	How does PFYC protect children's privacy?
We are concerned about the safety of children on the Internet. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.
If we become aware that a account holder is under the age of 13, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files.
NOTE TO CHILDREN UNDER 13: YOU ARE NOT ELIGIBLE TO USE THE SERVICES OR PURCHASE PRODUCTS ON THIS SITE. PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE US WITH ANY INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF.
7A.	What about links to other web sites and services?
The PFYC Sites may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These Web sites have their own policies regarding privacy, which you should review before visiting them. We bear no responsibility for linked Web sites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
8A.	How does PFYC.com have my consent to use this information?
By using the PFYC Sites, you consent to the collection and use of this information by PFYC in the manner described in this Policy.
Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted on the Web site to ensure that our customers understand how their information is being collected, used and disclosed.
Join Our Newsletter
Receive the latest news on new promotions, exclusive offers, and new arrivals.
Join
Copyright © 2020 PFYC-PartsForYourCar.
